Emmanuel! God is with us! My name is salami D. And my name is Justin.
Viewers all over the world, we welcome you to today's episode of changing lives.
In this program we are going to take you beyond the testimony to the heart of how life was and how life is,
after an encounter with Jesus Christ through the Ministry of Prophet TB Joshua.
Yes, throughout human history we have seen that those who bless God in their trials will be blessed by God through their trials and
through this interview we will listen to people's real-life trials how they responded how they overcame through God
And why they are rejoicing in the Lord today, and why you too can. Yes and today,
we will have the pleasure of speaking with the Ipusu's.
Their experience of marriage had been a difficult one that would rub the faith of almost everyone.
Today, God's grace has united them with the unshakable peace and love.
Their incredible journey, along the highway of marriage, seemed to end even before it had begun.
Not knowing that the challenges and the trials they were going through in their
relationship were only the tip of the iceberg. Their story is an eye
opener to the real cause of why many marriages don't work out today;
ultimately leading to divorce and how the bitter taste of life's trouble can be replaced with the sweetness of God's grace.
So be blessed as you join us in Jesus name. So, here, with us on changing lives,
we have our special guests with us here today.
Mr.. And Mrs. Ipisu's. You're very welcome. How are you today?
Fantastic so we'll start off with Dosu Ipisu. Can you introduce yourself to us and share with us your wonderful testimony.
Thank you very much. My name is Dosu Ipisuper
My testimony is about how I had lost affection for my husband and my experiences before and after my marriage
And then tracing back, before I got marriage: what you hear about marriage is
more like something smooths, the bed of roses,
fun fair, you know. How many stories you hear about people getting married.
How do they go for honeymoon and that was a dream for me as a young lady.
And then I met my husband, Mr Peter. He came along. We dated.
We had fun times up to the moment he said he wanted to marry me.
That was pic of hell in my life because
at that moment, he irritated me so much. I hated him more.
You know, he disgusted me. That's all I understood. At some point, I told him that why it must only be me.
What is so special about me. And I had a lot of psychological problems.
Thinking "why is this happening to me and all of that?''
And then I related to my parents and they told me that I should keep up with it. He's a good man.
Why not go a head and I told them : I don't have affection so how do I live with somebody that I don't love?
They keep telling me that love grows by the day. I told them let me back off from there now.
And hope that it comes on better.
But ,you know, it got more difficult.
Then just three days to my traditional marriage ,
I told him bluntly I'm not
going to marry him. Then my mom heard this she was like:'' oh my daughter, please,
you know, this is a dream for every mother to see her child get married.
And in my own case, I told her:'' for any reason whatsoever if you give him your consent;
then you're going in for the marriage".
So I related to him: you young man, I am not getting married to you.
I told him that bluntly and that's not easy to digest, you know! Three days to your marriage. It goes well.
He's going for the traditional marriage so, whether or not I come there it should be it fine,
get married if not he will walk away.
And so I fought that through until the day of our traditional marriage.
I finally got married against my will, anyway, I just did that out of play, jokes...
to just please my parents and
let peace be.
And so I felt okay, after the marriage
I will experience some peace, maybe, just like my father promised that love will come and will grow by the day.
We will get to do things that would get me into... but that never happened.
It will shock you to know that it got worse my dear.
Just seeing him, it would irritate me.
His sight's structure, I hated it. You with this pot-bellied where are you going too.
With stuff like that, and then he added it up with drinking.
He made it worse because I couldn't stand the odour.
He always stinks when he comes around. And in that kind of mood, he wants to crab jokes with me.
I never found anything funny. Even though he did his best. He would buy gifts when coming back home.
I didn't give into that kind, whether he gave me diamond, it didn't count. You know, I just wanted him to stay away.
Like this is a new marriage, you would like your husband around. He's not around you will miss him, you're
calling him. " Where are you? I didn't . In fact, it was fun for me when he was out. I had a great time when he
wasn't at home. So that went on
until, we start moving around, looking for solutions.
We felt everything wasn't just normal. We went to prayer houses,
we went, at his own side, he went to herbalists houses.
And then he came back telling me. Oh you are possessed.
They told me that" you're possessed with a spirit husband, and it's because you are possessed".
that's why, even at my workplace things are not moving or well for me. It's because you are possessed
that is why my car broke down, my business is not moving well.
And for your information, you will not have children.
More, so, reality will soon dawn on you. I'm quoting him now. "You know, he told me reality will soon dawn on you".
And then I taught myself, what am I doing in this place? Of what use am I in this place?
I am a woman who is not going to have kids. Your certificate will not get you anything.
I mean, I'm causing more trouble than good in this place, so I better excuse myself.
Being who he is I knew that I couldn't live that marriage,
when he was around. I mean any time he was at home with me.
I could not live and so I took my time.
I was monitoring properly, and I knew exactly
when I was going to hit this.
You know. I just knew exactly when he was going to go out. How many hours he would have to spent?
wherever he went and it was on a Sunday. I had arranged with people out there, to come and pack my things.
When he went out I brought a vehicle. I packed each and everything. I mean
to the very last pin, I brought in to do my part, and that was my attention never to return.
What the am I coming back to do in this house?
When I'm not bringing any joy, I was not a fulfilled woman, not a satisfied woman.
So what was the reason for staying in the house?
So I packed with the intention of never coming back to the house.
I didn't give any room whatsoever for conversation. I mean that no chance for him to call me.
Just not occur to me cope I didn't give in at me if you called me if I when I left the house of
Up to two months, I didn't pick his calls.
You know I have that capacity.
Just when I want to do it, I do it properly. He would call me, I saw those calls.
At times, I blocked him from calling m, some times, I doing some favor by letting the phone ring why don't peek?
You sent text messages that day my phone
I never replied to one you know there were there wasn't any form of
Communication was ever that was because I didn't want any resolution
And then my parents want to donate. Chip in I told them hey
Enough is enough. I had this before getting into the marriage and it cost me this pain so
What what do you think whatever advice you're giving me now do me any good
And so it it looked like I was
Getting too stubborn
Nobody could approach me
but then again, I felt I should take my time and
sick for God's face and
Then I'll know the will of God for my own marriage
I've gone to many churches of course. It's not like didn't pray for me of course. It did the best I could
But then I didn't get the expected results
Didn't I didn't get good years. I and for so I said I
Will give one last Trier and that place is the single God Church of All Nations?
Not because I was coming to look
Was sick for Prophet TB Joshua. No he's ma'am what I like myself
But I was coming too sick for that God
he dies using
multi I
Said this to my husband. Oh well finally I picked up my call. I told him for any reason whatsoever
If we are to combat together inking then we have one last mission together
Which is to travel down to Singapore Church of All Nations and by any chance we get there?
and
I don't get delivered to the points where our experience changes myself
I'll make my marriage better
Then issue count ourselves
divorced and then again, I said
If I'm up what shown to me the man of God I would like to find out from him what?
Is the will of God about this marriage because I remember he says
always that in whatever situation
You are going through God is still saying so
And as a good Christian
Surely seek to know what is God's opinion about the situation that was only reason
Why we had to come together and travel together talk together
Just do all of those were cared to us
Just commit to synagogue. It wasn't because I love you. No it wasn't any of those
I knew what I wanted and all of that of those
You might look at it. Did the wedges you know?
plastic makeup kind of things just to come to Synagogue Church of All Nations and to God be the glory I
Think I would simply sing cause time is the best
You know even Aquinas, and I'll go we'll see cost time is the best time at time doesn't matter so I'll simply see
God met me this time I came
And finally I was privileged to be prayed for by the man of course so yeah after you were married
It got to a point in your marriage where you decided to separate for how long were you separated
Before you decided that synagogue was the last bus stop that you seek the face of God at the synagogue Church of All Nations for
pray
By the we were married by December with three years in a marriage, and I left the marriage
empress extent
the came here this month, so it's it's about five months I
separated from the marriage
and then when I came here, I was privileged to be touched by the man of God like I said and
that
touch
Is that the actually while - I did manifest it?
You know I just knew that something was speaking through me
But I couldn't control it you know. I I really didn't want to act out we you know, but I couldn't control it and it
manifested
Eventually I go deliver, and I went back my husband who was prayed for and after then you know
unlike before
That I don't want him around completely
Right now me seemed like just when he steps out like hey boy. Where are you you know him to come back?
What's he doing? I want to be involved. You know every step of the way like I now care
I now have something to discuss with him. It wasn't like that before
Like he brings up sis gist and I'm like work out right don't you have something better to say?
You know I would be like
What's that?
How do I relate to these things you were saying, so I I never I never enjoyed his conversations his jokes
His gifts, you know he's and I was who
was
Boy with so much of those kids so him is there's so much by never valued it
after the prayer and it need to think if those I appreciated his efforts I
Acknowledged that she loved me. You know I felt somebody cared for me
I felt loved I was I felt some satisfaction in me you know even though
They see some hitches there of course. It's not a bed of roses
It's life generally and that goes for everybody every relationship. It's not always smooth
you always have those patches along the way, but then you know after that prayer I
Saw those problems in a different light and then my approach to them was also different
Unlike before you know it brought us
Troubles give me headaches, give me cause to worry what am I doing? It is well now?
I now realize that it's not him who is a problem. I'm sure this is happening order homes, too
You have those problems of quarantine you don't evoke really always arguing
You always irritated. You don't know if your husband may hear, and maybe the feel is normal. I'm
Here to tell them to the eats is not normal. It's not a normal about it
There's something wrong somewhere and your husband or your wife is not the problem no deeper
You would find
who is engineering all of this and fights that element else you'll be fighting the wrong battle and
you will never
Be victorious, I did today and because it almost happened to me
You know it ought not to almost wrecked my marriage
But now you know I now know how to approach it better in the light of God
To see that it is the enemy who is putting up these ads through him. You know just don't want Mitch
he has just simply come to steal my joy and
Make him make me feel like he's not what's it? What the hell am I doing with him? It's not him
It's the enemy who does not want my happiness who does not want us to enjoy it in marriage who does not want us to?
Leave a Christ Ward life because he knows that when he disables you where your mind is not at rest
We are no more
Happy within you because your heart is your prayer room
As soon as it disturb Eliza's your heart it gets you thinking it gets you
You know doing some some weird things that you know supposed to do
He knows that as soon as it does that
He has distorted your prayer life
And so you can be able to fight back rather you see the man or the woman as the problem
so now after that touch I
Deliverable thoughts how
how to handle my problems in the light of God yeah, okay, so
Looking back now. Can you now say?
Maybe you've now regretted do things your own way then
Remember you did so many things
Hot that'll be home, yeah
But later on you now, thought okay? Yes, you need to see the face of God
Looking back now. I
Wouldn't see I regret exactly not because I'm a Christian I would no have challenges
Or I will not have time petitions in fact
When those temptations come rather that just renting me
because one of God sees our
feet
Is tested upon the soil of?
Troubles trials and it flourishes upon that soil and so for a Christian that I taught I used to be
God won't count that as a mystic
Because I've come back to him to seek his face if I'd remain in
Diverse was suppression like I did
Then I'll be condemned
But I thank God for the Holy Spirit that also reminded me that that is not my place
The devil is all is trying to shift me away from my son ship
He's trying to shift maybe from my city and God's presence, and so I I simply bless God for bringing me back home
I call it back home because I
Wonder. What would have happened if I didn't come back and then again
I wonder how I would have known if this trials don't go because with this
like I said
I've learned how to approach the problems better because because I'm delivered now does not mean they will not come again
So God has simply told me on time that I should expect more, but then this is how best to
Handle them. It's right thing got some wonderful
wisdom
You've shared with us as well. We just want to take you back
what was your experience when Prophet TB Joshua prayed for you and
Had you ever received that kind of touch before in the past as soon as a prophet prayed for me
There was something different
In fact the first experience was that I had a very wonderful sleep
You know I had I felt coming my spirit. I felt some peace my spirit first. That was the first
experience that night
And then I woke up the next morning you know
Like me before. That's too diverse I
Wake up in the morning as soon as I turn to see them just beside this my oh hell. No what is this again?
It's not happening again. I just hit his sight just sighting alone
It is just pause my dear you know
Why woke up before him that the end? He was still sleeping lunch. You know I some picaros looking I
House is this really me? It's you lying here. You think you for you this month. There's more tree dentist. You know I
I was just sentence to myself I
Like me the past
I'm possibly move out of slap him like his we copies
Debris courage II you know just just a combatant have your dessert series, so now I'll have the house to myself
You just have my space
Onehand I will coffee doesn't like that. You know. I I don't want to disturb his sleep
I was a very much like oh you really come mine. You know recent you could keep up with all of this
You know I start pre shooting from dominance
That actually he's my husband, and I meant to love him and appreciating for whatever
It's doing for me, so I felt that difference immediately. I can't see as instant as possible that night
No, we thank God Almighty for this
Incredible deliverance and the changes that have taken place in your life. You can really see that it was that evil spirit
that was behind the
The destruction of that marriage and so what want to do now, I want to hear from mr.
Peter now and hear your side of their testimony as well
Thank you very much. My name is Pete. I pursue and I'm from Denver states. I'm a happy man today
because I've been through a lot I
Knew my wife
We stayed together
lived in one room
Slept on one bed for two years I
Had to change my
Z to be I wanted our to served she agreed hard time
Played together had a lot of romance
One thing we never did was she told me young my aunt marry me as yeah, so she said
If truly I'm serious. I don't marry her I should become
the nursing my sometimes who fight
Namah namah were best of friends
So when I decided to be serious with the relationship after two years. I met I'm a
20 2012 or together 2013 by the end of it
2010 when I decided to marry that was the beginning of my troubles with my wife
When I'm not there I could talk was my low for a comparators kind of 1/5. Talk to her the card is finished
As soon as she set her eyes on me
They'll be trouble I was drinking that I was lying to my sinking
So one of those days a Saturday friend. Oh, we're discussing boy aunt Marion. This is the trouble and
For
About those years that I've lived on earth. I've never ever in my life. This is that a width:auto
Because I grow up from a Catholic home
Eventually when I got there I
Discovered that it was a spiritualist. I so I'm yeah. I can't go back. Let me get to know I sat down
And they told me the trope was not behind my marriage my wife was not meant to marry
Past relationship is what are you going after? I know that I know that so I should bring a folk reason
They'll do some concourse and give us who take and then every to be over
So I came back to LA she was
Discourses haha she said over her dead body
She will never visit any witch doctor for any reason
The herself I suspected that something is wrong with her. How kind of beautiful my
Youngest to get married to somebody who loves you
Here might show her love and nice type of marriage and phase one
All right sure sir found the place. We are suppose we for prayers
So she say instead of going to the house craft witch doctor we should visit her man of God or reach in there
now man of God said
They say
75 to 80% of the teens I was toward so I believed her I
Believe that so we're going dia
best changes were no economy
Changes were not coming my wife could look at me in the face
When I decided husband tomorrow she told me that I have no affection for you it was cool
But because I hadn't knowledge or what the problem was and this woman of God have told us what the problem was inevitable
Okay, just tell us
When you first met yeah for how long was the relationship going really well for two years for two years
And then at what point did you realize that?
this was a spiritual problem, and it was not normal at what point two years and then
What I decided to marry her when I proposed to her. I took out somewhere to propose to her but
She said God is difficult for her to get Israel she loves me, but she has no affection for me
She loves me she knew cause me goodness and me that she has no affection for me
And that I one of God told us a lot of things and that's one very fundamental in Douma said I can be moving
What's your complexion or fecha Lamar said?
family affection
Mera kaam
So if I live we live a prayer place and go, but we were running around
She will agree
Few days after she said no
So a few days after she said no and that the events now happening cross. I just knew that it was an omen
Of let me let me just quickly chip in there at the point where he says I agreed and a nice
No, you know what we got to this woman
She's a prophetess their fellowship with so when he said she gets to have her beliefs. I said we should go to the woman
Do something she said to me she said
If I don't get married to my husband then I'll never get married in my life
And so you know I had all of this going through my mind, so if I don't get married to this man
I'm not going to get married
Because when I went to high I was confused and I told her that please I want you know if this - my husband knows
Exactly what took me in there
So when when we finally got there?
She told me that any man
I'll bring to the church that is my husband and eventually I was taking my husband did not
- see he's my husband, but because of the problems we had and he discovered it at happiness
And then so I told him that ok
Let's seek the face of God which I had our talents in also getting there
And then she telling me that if I don't get married to this man. I was never going to get married
That's also compounded my problem. You know to think of idiots
my flesh is saying no to this my the same times the
Prophetess who sees better than I do is telling me that if I don't get married to this man
I will never get married so it compounded my problem and made me act the way I did off
You know I would say yesterday say no tomorrow
Like that so three days to our traditional marriage. I was in a house
About some time it was such me the father the modern high myself
We are ready how the next three days would be
She told her mother in my presence
now if the mother agrees the mother's got to marry me and she walked out on me the father and mother I
Really
Took my car what to town had seven bottles of beer that
Was about 11:00 p.m.. From Baku doors where I've been to Makati
that from bukata Makati almost killed myself I ran it a
Ditch that's oh I wasn't wrong
They tried to dodge it Drella I ran into that pit and I stayed after 2 a.m.. I drove to my car
D630 the money a friend of mine
Was there was close Ross?
Knew that hardcore and for the next three days came to the house
And I told him two stories or not as a pastor when it was cinema
637 hours in our pastors church
The next day another friend of mine book was calling me calling me calling me
And then eventually the guy drove to my Cody and I showed him where I was in the church
What we reach out to say oh boy what they do again
Okay, tell us mr.
Fitta at that point in time when your wife to be
Told she was no longer interested in married three days to the wedding. Yes, actually. What's your reaction then I wanted to make history
Hmm, I wanted to make history. I want to make a history that a beautiful girl a queen you
know
quaint like this
the young has come to Maya and
She refused to come out. No. I don't give I know
That other people say off you go you run away. I also give him in need
so
I kept it fit so
It was in fact it was
two days to our traditional marriage that
She agreed. I can I was not pictures did so many as four people two days if you look at those pictures are very funny
Sorted are you?
Convinced he knows a tremendous respect for her father
Sir tremendous respect for her and she felt she
Zuba disappointed me because the the younger wants a rope whatever said that me the house. I didn't use chance on there
You know I could be tired
Let me know so soma soma
Go go married
during our traditional marriage
The whole mother half of the church were working for prayers we're at the back
praying for us
But a lot of things happened
Within this time were dogs on work that were hard money somewhere
The work that she was doing an hour's dream
She had some good money somewhere and my owners refused opium
So we started looking for me at the border, and then you know God have a way of doing things
It will closed we're off a then go to Joe's open always small noise
Okay, so you finally got married after your marriage? What were the challenges and issues you are facing?
Yeah
If I began to say or just cause the challenges I faced
Yet
but the remarkables a
Married this beautiful me
For three to four months I have not met her husband our lives. What was leaving the room like toys
To appoint her to console me my office to talk to her
That's
There was no changes to a point
This is very intelligent that own or Dysport she started
Living a plastic life with me
She wanted it, but you know
What you're not being from your heart?
At a point where oh do it?
Angle cone angle setting and that will disappear
That led me into massive massive intake of alcohol
I've married I sat down
I've paid a bride price. I've told Gordon the church. You are my wife
Why can't I meet your old man? How I?
So I want it massive drinking my office walls are supposed to start by 8:00 8:30. I'll leave the house 7 o clock
The first place obviously to be by Apollo sometimes I end up not going to the office
How's tea I'll drink some days, I'll come back some days sometimes
I'll come back two days after three days after
same clothes
After can record this part of the town to Murom drive it rather a part of the town sim clue so dark
Those people saw me yesterday. Oh those clothes are not seen in design. They today. I'm another part
and then when I get home a
Cretan environment, yes, you could ask me am I coming from
Because I told her you're sending me away from the house, so you have no right to ask me. I'm coming for a
common path I
Develop a techniques of moving up a project with a body my car so that I won't have a problem of changing my clothes
How drink
Sometimes I will sit sleepy Apollo. I will not be drinking that our local. I had the capacity to
Drink from money tonight on a two-day break
And no joints that starts by 10:00 p.m.
So when I finish the joints are closes by 9:00 or 10:00. I moved to the one that starts by 10:00 p.m.
To 6:00 a.m.. I
Invested my money into alcohol and
The devil ever worked many things it's the person who said the devil who of the things
He will lead you to those friends that
Will add to your predicaments that you take your foolish with that you'll do yourself good
Because it harder, we'll celebrate
However, they knew that if they call me. They will give me one, but two bottles and our deaf I cut off
Because they knew that I am never tired and I said I want to go home
So those are the kind of friends that the devil brought into my life at a time I
Was into drinking even after my investing in 2006 and so I was still very slim like you are
When I got married I
didn't even give out opportunity of
Telling me there's no joy
So and that's why you find out a lot of young people
Today you see their Envy Apollo's find out a body a home something is wrong
gossiping to me has happened to me and so that's actually give us trouble I
Knew that's it does that the test of alcohol that was my best friend I
Can't pick my best friend when I called her to ask me
It were to a point if I get home axilla, what are you even doing in this house?
What are you doing in this house pack your things I'll leave by Quixote's I give me space
You know and I
Was said I bless go together. I please go today so wonderful a
Woman was married in mind you have no affection always for
Then you're leaving the room with a person for three years. It's not three days. We're talking about
Who did this three years
ago comes
As well sit in yanaka tell her how many times of smite?
To smile with each other I can tell you
three years
Okay, mr. Pizza
Can I just actually a quick one it's about all the?
Difficulties you were passing through you are facing what called veins
Do you not give up on the marriage because evening those in who is Kraft told me that if my wife is fully delivered
I'm going to enjoy my own
But the devil actually
Blindfolded me not to seek God in the right way not to seek to redeem my marriage in the right way
I will visit one little doctor to the order to attend maternity
Obviously the man of God who can give professes that any dissenting, but the problem was still there, so
The perfect we work and moving is God
God wanted to do annuity in our lives God wanted to use meaning
As yoga pose to teach the world like what gender now?
To let them know that it is better and best in Christ
but
Which were a lot to a point I?
Look at again. I also have a word less privilege
Not less privilege because were from a poor
but
You not be able to stand out of my OMA, and I'll get to see I know I appreciate me
I'll look at the one that is more than her a good clue so her to appreciate me
And then I knew that something was actually wrong in my own
Today and celebrity her as a mother of my children a raccoon
This hat has
My daughter is going to have part of it because it is not easy for a woman was not affection for you
2004 three years
three years
Whatever, I will tell you that go home manage. Ah at the end of the days of the tour for now I
Didn't come but in these three years so not to divert attention
For me, okay, can you tell us?
Mentioned earlier that you separated for five months, what led you to
Finally seeking the face of God at the synagogue Church of All Nations
Between you and your wife our God is a merciful God
their message of God
Would leave in Makati yeah, hi long way down, and I would leave the house for three days
Oh, no come back. She was there docile
so when she left I
Decided to stay indoors, and I regretted every minute of what I did was he down on me
This more gear inside this house all alone
I'll come back or not I get she will humbly come
And I was caught harder at the turn of the road she saw wasn't no the son of my car
But in this time I sent a text messages that we're covering rates. She didn't respond and of them
What did you speak to each other for 37 days? I was counting I
Know the circumstances that led to certain things actually told Nina something was wrong on my wedding day hard accident
On my wedding day
Nobody was driving the car. I parked the car was talking to somebody at it cost at a movie
I dusted it was he parked. I told my house
And I wanted to find out where she was yeah housing book. I heard resident
So a lot of things happened that I fed one on nama
as I said let us seek the face of God I
Appreciated pathos that prayed for us. They did a wonderful job
But I think God was preparing us to give us a testimony. We are we are today?
And so I have even received hours
I have seen snow prophet to be just a humble man. They coincide Holmes
Wonder forms now Sam
I was a pretty wife on that test when I watch I think for 30 years 35 years
Because idea God was able to look at that
So it was when she left the audience that I committed me
Ecstatic on me to me
And so she has watching. Anywhere is God. She will go a new you the name of God is national shoulder
So wait this cousin, and she told me that she's tired of go to prayer houses
The only place she go now if it is synagogue she's ready
That was where our finances
Brenda did ever knew that food gets here will be set free
Every other person I discusses I why do you need to go to synagogue, not I have synagogue in Makati
Those pastors and pray for us that my wife. Don't want to be unreasonable. I never give up
So I did all I could I
Left pleasure to seek God and
eventually who Katya I
Will cut his sentence significant happen
something that Oh God when I buy it I
Want to gas every minute you want a study piece I have in my heart today
I'm like I'm I'm already feeling like a billionaire because peace in my heart
When I came I came with it, what would this thorn in my heart
If you look at me, you will know that house more happy to a point. I I was a civil a man time I
could be a bedroom slippers and
Go outside your house something I never did before
If you're always not settled a gone you're gone. You can never find peace
How did you feel when you saw that your wife was receiving deliver oh my goodness
You know something happened
Happened all the people pray for my wife. She said I said
troubles room and
immediately
The man of course you know I was lucky that I got it was when a man of God before her
So when I got a touch I felt relief instantly it's not magic
It's not magic
It's not magic. I feel relief so I was walking happily out
And then I had a sound and when I talked to the television dollar close to me
I saw my wife manifest and say thank you Jesus
Immediately I saw that I said, thank you Jesus. I knew that the end has come
The end of our troubles are
So when she came out I pretended I
Pretended she could hold it
you know from
The deliverance point to the hotel where I was staying
She had my heart. I said Jesus. What is happening. This is real
So what all she wanted was to pray I she asked me to lead in the prayers I
Said I'm so attached to pray
She said a very short prayer. Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Jesus. Thank you Jesus, and I said
Was left like babies Wow
She woke up, I didn't know that she woke up before me I
Sue litera when I woke up. I saw her sitting on the bed. I was looking at
That ice that I tend I look at her that first day after to leave us on the bed touch my heart
As I said, what's in that finished me to say?
Thank you for not giving up, and I said, thank you for you are into
That was the thinking that was the day I would add my wife
Would ask you. You know if it was before she says smelly mouth
Without process, she kissed me that money. I said Jesus. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you Wow
That was if it were before
Smelly mouth please excuse me
She had kissed me got any money kiss without brushing
And I knew that God has finally if you stirred my home
God has finally said my home
Has been wonderful, and I thank God that I never give up if I had missed this woman
I don't think I said I found another woman in this war but
Thank you so much
Glory so now tell us, how is the marriage now?
If I start telling you disappearances were experienced in this one or two weeks will not live here
Do you know we're now create together we eat together while walking on the road?
Welcome I didn't know she was carrying a Roman aromas which I had
Only after the deliverance add my you know I wanted to be sure of what has happened I
Will protect, I leave the hotel go behind stay
Five minutes ten inches cause on the Bizon this way you come back
But this come back now was more realistic than that of when it was plastic
It was plastic
See no longer uses me derive a potbelly so tell me that I walk on this our stomach I was too much
Before my now, it's our
You know so good
Whoa do you have any discussions at all now can bring all the topic from the Bible and discourse
So it's not
Do it before a costly now try to find out to see her reaction. It's wonderful
Thank God for this indifference we can really say the it's a new marriage now. Yeah, but yourself as well
You know you're having that problem of drinking alcohol you say you could drink from morning tonight after the prey
Do you still have that urge to drink alcohol after the prey us the next day?
We're living out to get some silly road, that's what people drink as they look our fools
They're fooling themselves
Don't talk about top of the food is shed as the current users
so this is what I was doing I
hid the smell of alcohol
Through swab Amana TV my state, and I watching me
to celebrate
because they know that
if me
Come attend work day that I no longer drink alcohol. It doesn't leave
I'm telling you
Because know what the devil did its point my home completely hmm sport now so now
Absolutely there's peace
You know you can't fake this
I can't figure as peace
You know I and I understand why people
Wanna go I'm not saying that those who pray for us before they didn't it didn't do work
You did your part well God want us to want that also get out deliverance
We thank God Almighty for this radical transformation that has come in your marriage
And we know our viewers are watching and we know they have been blessed by all
They are shared with them, and they also have questions. They want to ask you which I?
Like to ask you and then maybe we would answer them and share more lighter than what you're saying okay?
so we have a question from one of our viewers and
It says
My name is Calista from New Zealand and the question goes to you mr.. Peter it says
When crisis hits your marriage you run - how cool
So like many do so what did you learn from that and what advice can you give to others about that?
Yeah, some days. That's a
Crisis hits you
Okay, well you're not Rocco or you know these abilities you rather destroy yourself on your soul I?
Wouldn't read I destroyed myself
But finishes my peace at home and all that so, but we're on to Christ today
I'm celebrating because I'm fully God Christ
so nobody
Don't body should receive you that when you have crisis rock or you can forget it
For one minute you forget it the next minute. It will come more. It's rather increase your crisis
Today I have not our life, but our crisis crisis
Life with Christ you have absolute peace
absolute necessity
Okay, so we have
Another question and it's for the both of you. It's from Steve from Canada and
he says
Me and my partner have been dating for more than a year now
And we are looking to tie the knot what advice do you have for us?
First DLC
Yet to tie the knots you should avail yourself for deliverance
But that's I mean
Probably you feel you're alright even physically. There's nothing wrong with you, and of course the bottle fee
I enjoy yourself, but I'm just telling you this even gue passes through fire
should be what it is and
So you shouldn't think all this rosin all is okay? He's just
By the side there isn't so I've been yourself the both of them for deliverance first before going into the marriage
Yeah, and for those who are married already all of us need deliverance
No force need deliverance you may be fully yourself thinking that mr.. A is the problem mr.. B is the problem
There's a spirit behind
every circumstances that happens
In our lives today. I can't testify to that
so to say your husband-to-be
Is a problem already it's a problem or your wife? I wrongly accused my wife
Even don't know fortunately they deliver us
But that should not happen physical, huh?
Should I read a sect God for deliverance?
Was it wasn't getting live at every other Court in comes your way today. I'm enjoying it I
Wish I had taken disturb years back
The cost time is said to be the best so this is his time
so I appreciate and
We are going for deliverance
Go to deliverance in a life spirit church
If your pot you come to synagogue
Nobody should deceive you no, but this man is a man of God. I'm a practical example to that I
Can't testify before the world war two did he say my eyes never met me it's like before doesn't know anything about
I don't know anybody in synagogue
the doctors
Relieved my ass coming to synagogue with my wife. I said protect couples to deal with kiss on the road
See I said it from the beginning
And she left that was no one never to come back that today was big one is sharing my experiences
joyful movements
Fine expiry free choice if you can't come to synagogue we went to so many places are they prayed for us
Some became very angry with us. How are you physically? Yeah the Word of God?
The effect that they have to live others. Also don't do what we need to do
That touch 4g b ja ja
This is purified charge. You'd be a living testimony you go back and testify
Thank you very much here for
Sharing your time with us here on changing lives
absolute incredible advice and this is a new marriage now in Christ Jesus and
Wonderful advice. We believe this testimony is going to touch
Millions of marriages and people that are about to be married
Around the world as well. Thank you very much. Thank you for
Here about my reach. It's more like your physician test smoothes the better fools is
Fair you come in stories you hear about people getting married before honeymoon and all the dream for me to escape in
2010 when I decide that my
That was the beginning of my troubles of my wife we had fun times up to the moments when he said you intend to marry
me at that point in time when your wife to be the
Holding. She was no longer interested in marry you three days to the wedding. Yes actually
What's your reaction, then I wanted to make history just three days to my traditional marriage. I
Told him bluntly I'm not playing tomorrow. Let's see him, and he cheated me
He sighs structurally I hated him and like who unity spot very very good
What was your experience when Prophet TB Joshua prayed for you as soon as a prophet treat for me
It was something different right now me seemed like just when he steps out like a boy
Why do you have this problems of quarantine don't about the enormous?
Adhering you've always irritated all of us by God me and maybe the famous Sonoma
I'm here to tell them to be it sees motional at the Saltaire, Oksana
Well what a wonderful
testimony and the life of mr. And mrs
Apostle and we believe that there are many lessons that you learn from it
You know that unfavorable situations the great arguments that Satan uses to make children of God to question their sonship
Question their marriage and other areas of their life and even question if what they are doing is the will of God for their lives
The fact that you are a child of God does not eliminate
Adversity such as the circumstances that happened in their marriage, but rather being a child of God
Turns that adversity into an opportunity
For God to manifest his glory in that situation yes viewers
We believe you are seen in their experience that God can use any situation
I mean any foolish thing for his purpose and bring good out of evil what seem like evil in the face of the painful
experience of chronic disagreements
Disgust and hatred was eventually used by God to strengthen their determination and desire for him
yes, what Satan meant for bad God made it work for good and this testimony has taught us that we need to rest in a
place that God has for us, so that his grace can cover us, so if you find yourself in a situation that is contrary to
Expectations in Christ don't budge
don't pull out stay put and get used to that situation so that you can gain the necessary experience a maturity to handle the
responsibilities in Christ so viewers
Whatever situation you are facing in your marriage should not break it
But rather strengthen it and your marriage can only be strengthened by you've run into Jesus Christ for he is the great
Deliverer thank you very much for joining us and changing lives. My name is Justin and my name is Solomon
II thank you once again for joining us on this program changing lives and don't forget to join us on the next
Episode which will be coming very soon
and also viewers
We know you also have a testimony to share you can send us your testimony through idot's emmanuel dot TV
We want to listen to your testimony's because we believe your own testimony can also bless others. Thank you once again
Thank you very much